Davis Land

PROFILE

Current student of telecommunications, media studies, and computer science with experience in broadcasting, publishing, and event organizing. Passionate about artistic storytelling and providing a voice where one may not exist.

510 Thornton Ct. College Station, TX, 77840 (903) 920-9269 dland95@tamu.edu davisland.info

EXPERIENCE

KANM Student Radio, College Station, TX

Programming Director - December 2014 to Present

• Oversee show scheduling, FCC compliance, DJ attendance and show logs.

DJ - September 2013 to Present

Produce weekly two hour radio show. Conduct interviews in-studio with bands.

KEOS Community Radio, Bryan, TX - DJ/Volunteer - August 2014 to Present

- Produce two weekly two hour radio shows.
- Review music for library inclusion and air play.

Write About Now, Houston, TX - Producer, Podcast Host - December 2014 to Present

- Assist in audio and video recording for the Write About Now YouTube channel and podcast.
- Produce weekly half-hour podcast featuring poets at a weekly poetry slam in Houston, TX, submit to iTunes.

Mic Check Poetry, Bryan, TX - Vice President, CFO - March 2014 to Present

- Coordinate and ensure effective action pertaining to Mic Check's 501(c)(3) non-profit and financial status.
- Assist President in duties such as management of the Texas Grand Slam Poetry Festival and various Arts Council
 programs.

The Eckleburg Project, Texas A&M's Student Literary Journal, College Station, TX

Poetry Editor and Officer - May 2014 to Present

- Lead and manage poetry team in selecting the poetry sections of each semester's journal.
- Work with officer board to plan for each semester as well as make decision pertaining to the future of the magazine.

Poetry Screener - September 2013 to May 2014

Select the poetry section of each semester's journal from a pool of submitted student writing.

Mostly Water, Independent Literary Journal, Bryan, TX - Editor-In-Chief, Founder - October 2014 to Present

- Coordinate with staff in designing and curating and editing the journal, maintaining online brand and presence.
- Manage local, statewide, national, and international direct distribution and bookstore distribution.

Target, College Station, TX - Trainer and Team Member- December 2014 to Present

- Arrive before store opening to unload delivery truck, stock store with merchandise.
- Oversee stocking team in training and effective day-to-day operation.

Chick-fil-A, Whitehouse, TX - Team Leader and Closer, Cashier - May 2010 to August 2013

 Assist night managers in store operation and closing procedures, ensure team members are taking and fulfilling orders efficiently, ensure guest satisfaction.

EDUCATION AND AWARDS/HONORS

Texas A&M University

B.S. Telecommunications and Media Studies; Minor: Computer Science
Major GPA: 3.0, Overall GPA: 2.8; Expected Graduation: December 2017

Excellence in Broadcasting Journalism Award Earned for outstanding work in Whitehouse High School's Broadcasting Journalism program.

Eagle Scout Earned Eagle ranking in the spring of 2013.

SKILLS

Skilled in Microsoft Word, Excel, and Powerpoint, Adobe Photoshop, InDesign, and Premiere. Experience and skill in audio/visual editing, graphic design, and document layout. Familiar with various hardware tools in audio/video recording and production as well as applicable techniques. Experience with C++, Python, HTML, and XML coding languages.

Davis Land 510 Thornton Ct. College Station, TX, 75703 • (903) 920-9269 • dland95@tamu.edu

REFRENCES

Erin Holesher; <u>Station Manager</u>, KANM Student Radio erinroseg22@gmail.com; (210) 845 - 0465

 $\label{eq:content_formula} \textbf{Florence Davies}; \underline{Administrator}, \textbf{The Texas A\&M University Writing Center}; \underline{Advisor}, \textbf{The Eckleburg Project fsdaviesog@tamu.edu; (281) 658-3627}$

 $\textbf{Brady Ware}; \underline{\text{Videographer}}, \\ \text{Write About Now Poetry}$

brady@softwaysolutions.com; (979) 421 - 3556

Bill Moran; Former President, Mic Check Poetry

billmoran68@gmail.com; (218) 467 - 4654